How did they become so good at this?
In your studies, how did white people become so good at the strategy of oppression on many climates?
It's not even like, well, we was good at this in Africa, but we don't know how to do it in Mexico.
The consistency and the efficacy of their oppressive manners is so prevalent that I find myself ever so often being like, this got to be supernatural.
Are they the aliens?
Because they're the only life on Earth that doesn't, that the sun doesn't help.
Is it cultural?
Some historians like talk about, you know, the dark ages in Europe and how there was just so much war.
When there's a tremendous amount of war anywhere in the world, what's going to happen is those people are going to develop better technologies to harm each other or to defend themselves.
And ironically, that's why when we see all these movies about like pre-modern Europe, it's always about war.
It really is always about war.
You just cracked a code.